Stephanie Viveros

I am a motivated software engineer with a passion for learning and thirst for continuous self-improvement. My previous experience in customer service and leadership positions has rewarded me with strong leadership abilities and communication skills. I hope to utilize my foundation, motivation, and passion to benefit your company.

Address: 3740 Towle Ave. Hammond, IN 46327 **Tel:** (219) 308 - 6499

Email: sviveros05@gmail.com

Portfolio:

midknight92.github.io/portfolio-stephanie_viveros/

Github: github.com/MidKnight92

PROJECTS

Battle-At-Sea — HTML5, CSS3, & JavaScript

- A two-player game inspired by Battleship
- Applied object-oriented programming and game logic

Fetch! — *MongoDB*, *Express*, & *Node.js*

- A full-stack app to help users find and recommend dog-friendly locations in their area
- Used Places API, integrated a document-oriented database API in a RESTful architecture

Love Talk — Flask & React

- A dating app, that creates user matches and allows them to send messages to one another
- Incorporated an SQLite relational database API

Second Chance — *MongoDB*, *Express*, *React & Node.is*

- An adoption awareness app, that shows and matches users to dogs that are currently in need of a home
- Utilized the Petfinder API, React Router, & Reactstrap

SKILLS

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Vanilla JS JQuery | Python | Node.js | Git | PostgresSQL ReactJS | MongoDB | Mongoose | Flask

EDUCATION

Purdue University Calumet, Hammond, IN — *B.A. Business*

2010 - 2014

$\textbf{Whiting High School,} \ \textbf{Whiting, IN} - \textit{General}$

2006 - 2010

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, Chicago, IL — Software Engineering Fellow

Sep. 2019 - Dec. 2019

- Utilized modern programming languages and technologies during a 12-week, full-time program
- Designed and built 4 web applications with emphasis on application flow, logic, and comments in a five-day stretch
- Envisioned, designed, created, and debugged applications both independently and as part of a team

U.S.Installers LLC, Hammond, IN — Business Owner

July 2018 - Sep. 2019

- Developed operation plans and business strategies
- Maintained day-to-day operation
- Maintained social media accounts

Starbucks Coffee Company, Schererville, IN — *Shift Supervisor*

May 2012 - Sep. 2019

- Lead and managed a team of 17 people
- Trained and mentored new and current partners
- Resolved customer complaints
- Voted Partner of the Quarter